This is Shantae Trumpet.
First week of February, Shantae Trumpet was on a train in D.C.,
looked out on the platform and saw bodies,
and then the doors opened and the shooter came on the train.
Y'all, the shooter told everybody,
you cannot leave or I will shoot you.
He sat down next to Shantae.
Shantae, being comfortable with firearms,
said to herself, I'm gonna disarm this man.
And in True Black Women Be Saving the World every day,
she did, and she's gonna be on Small Doses today
talking about her experience
and also talking about firearm awareness,
safety, and control.
The latest in our hero series,
Shantae Trumpet will be joining us on Small Doses today.
So send me your questions for Shantae Trumpet
about what was going through her mind,
about what her experience is with firearms,
about why she actually made it her business
to get comfortable with firearms.
Drop all of that in the comments right here.
Side effects of disarming a shooter.
You go, sis.